Hallo
Today I am going to show you how to pronounce German car names
I have heard a lot of people pronounce the car names incorrectly
And it makes me very angry
So for this I am going to teach you how to pronounce the car names correctly now
But first I must eat a Lebkuchen
So the first wrong car name so many people say
Audi
When it's actually pronounced Audi
Say it with me
Audi
Very easy
Next
BMW
In German you say BMW
It stands for Bayerische Motorwerke
Yeah?
It is not a funny term
It's not to make go and fun laugh
Okay?
In English this means
Bayerische Motorwerks
Very accurate name
More Lebkuchen
It's delicious I am enjoying it
Next
Mercedes Benz
Ah this makes me sick
I am going to have to open a beer
The name is pronounced Mercedes Benz
Now we get to one that really makes me very angry
I hear the name Porsche a lot
I will say this only once
In Germany we say Porsche
Good
I don't get this wrong again
Here is a toast to Porsche
Fun fact this is not beer this is pipiwasser
Because it is Swiss
Now we have one for all the preteen 16 year old girls
You say Opel
We say Opel
Like jeder Popel fährt einen Opel
This means every bugger drives an Opel
I am going to get to the last one
You say VW
In Germany we say VW
Get it right
This stands for Volkswagen
And it means the car of the people
Hello
Here is a bonus clip for you
I have seen lots of people have difficulty saying this name
We got the Koenigsegg
Swedish Koenigseggs
Koenigseggs
It is pronounced Koenigsegg
You are welcome
Good night